surveylaunch.com 2019-07-31

# Privacy

Survey Launch Co.  
Updated: 03/30/2018 

**Survey Launch Co. ("Survey Launch")**

This policy applies to the Survey Launch Corporate Internet site [www.surveylaunch.com](http://www.surveylaunch.com/). 

This privacy policy does not apply to the collection, processing, storage, transfer, and/or disposal of information collected in connection with the survey panels, surveys, applications, or communities operated by or on behalf of Survey Launch. Additional statements and policies can be found on those sites, as well as on our Privacy Shield Policy <http://www.surveylaunch.com/privacyshield/>. 

**Privacy Policy**

Survey Launch Co. respects your personal privacy and is committed to adhering to federal, state and international privacy laws as well as industry guidelines in order to protect you and your identity. This privacy policy describes what Personal Data is collected from you when you visit this website (the "Survey Launch website" or the "website"). This Privacy Policy applies only to the Survey Launch website (www.surveylaunch.com), not to any other sites that may be accessible from here. 

Please be sure to read this Privacy Policy before using the website or submitting information to us. By using the website, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. Please check this area periodically for updates to this Privacy Policy. If we make amendments to this policy we will post them here. 

**INFORMATION SURVEY LAUNCH COLLECTS FROM YOU**

**Personal Data**

When you visit the website, we will not collect any Personal Data or other sensitive information from you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. 

We collect information from users of our website by permitting you to communicate directly with us via email. Some of the information that you submit during this voluntary process may be personally identifiable. Specifically, that is information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your name, business name, address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address. In addition, in the process of doing business with us you may include other sensitive information such as financial or product information related to the services you wish us to provide you. Survey Launch does not authorize the use of any information you provide for any purpose other than to provide the services you request. Survey Launch will never sell or use this information for any purpose other than the intention for which you supplied it. 

**Passive Information Collection**

This website no longer uses Google Analytics and as such does not collect any passive information about visitors to the website. Survey Launch does not track IP addresses, use cookies, assign internet tags, or retrieve browser and operating system information. 

**HOW SURVEY LAUNCH USES YOUR INFORMATION**

Your contact, product and financial information will be used for the purposes for which you supplied it to us, to send you related notices or materials and to respond to your comments or requests for information. If you direct comments to us, or request information from us, we may ask you questions in an effort to tailor our response to your specific requests. 

Survey Launch will not sell or transfer your personally identifiable information to any third party for the third party's own use without your consent. Survey Launch may disclose your personal information to the reputable vendors that assist us in process of delivering requested materials or services. These vendors are not authorized to use the information for any purpose other than the purpose of delivering the services you requested. Survey Launch, however, shall have not have liability for disclosure of information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized intervention of third parties. 

Survey Launch may be required to disclose Personal Data in response to lawful requests from public authorities including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

**CHOICES YOU HAVE ABOUT HOW SURVEY LAUNCH USES YOUR INFORMATION**

You may contact us if you do not want your information to be used in the manner described in this Privacy Policy or wish to correct any information that you have provided to us. If you request a correction of your information, we will use reasonable efforts to make those corrections in a timely manner. 

**HOW SURVEY LAUNCH PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

We have implemented both technical and procedural methods to maintain the integrity and security of all Personal Data under our control and protect it against loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration. In addition, our electronic files are backed up for redundancy and designed to be accessible only by authorized individuals. 

This site may contain links to other websites operated by third parties that may be of interest to you. We cannot control these third party sites which may collect Personal Data from you. When you follow a link and leave this site, you do so at your own risk and are encouraged to review the privacy policy of the website you are visiting. 

**WHAT SURVEY LAUNCH DOES ABOUT CHILDREN VISITING THE WEBSITE**

This website is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. If a child has provided us with Personal Data, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us via e-mail at [privacy@surveylaunch.com](mailto:privacy@surveylaunch.com) if they would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our databases. 

**HOW YOU CAN CONTACT SURVEY LAUNCH**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of the website, please email [privacy@surveylaunch.com](mailto:privacy@surveylaunch.com), or telephone at 203.497.2560.
